<resources>
    <string name="app_name">فرحك</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Sign up now.</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registred! Login Me.</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="btn_logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="nav_item_attachment">Smartphones</string>
    <string name="nav_item_images">clothes</string>
    <string name="nav_item_location">Accessories</string>
    <string name="nav_sub_menu">SubMenu</string>
    <string name="nav_sub_menu_item01">sub item 1</string>
    <string name="nav_sub_menu_item02">sub item 2</string>
    <string name="drawer_header_text">Welcome</string>
    <string name="call_bottombar">اتصال</string>
    <string name="dummy_text1">ذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط هذا نص تجريبي لاختبار شكل و حجم النصوص و طريقة عرضها في هذا المكان و حجم و لون الخط</string>


     <string name="cheese_ipsum">Jarlsberg lancashire edam. Dolcelatte hard cheese brie st. agur blue
    cheese caerphilly bavarian bergkase cheese and biscuits mascarpone. Cheeseburger swiss bavarian
    bergkase cream cheese fromage frais cheesy feet port-salut airedale. St. agur blue cheese rubber
    cheese caerphilly cheddar cheesecake cream cheese manchego lancashire. Roquefort squirty cheese
    the big cheese.</string>
    <string name="checkin">Checkin</string>

    <string name="menu_night_mode">Night mode</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_system">Follow system</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_day">Day (always)</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_night">Night (always)</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_auto">Auto</string>



</resources>
